let savollar27 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "actually",
        answer: "A. aslida",
        options: [
            "A. aslida",
            "B. ehtimol",
            "C. go'yo",
            "D. balki"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "bite",
        answer: "B. tishlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. tamaddi",
            "B. tishlamoq",
            "C. o'pmoq",
            "D. yutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "coast",
        answer: "C. qirg'oq",
        options: [
            "A. tog'",
            "B. vodiy",
            "C. qirg'oq",
            "D. daryo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "deal",
        answer: "D. kelishuv",
        options: [
            "A. janjal",
            "B. muhokama",
            "C. muammo",
            "D. kelishuv"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "desert",
        answer: "A. cho'l",
        options: [
            "A. cho'l",
            "B. o'rmon",
            "C. orol",
            "D. daryo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "earthquake",
        answer: "B. zilzila",
        options: [
            "A. suv toshqini",
            "B. zilzila",
            "C. bo'ron",
            "D. olov"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "effective",
        answer: "C. samarali",
        options: [
            "A. samarasiz",
            "B. foydasiz",
            "C. samarali",
            "D. keraksiz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "examine",
        answer: "A. tekshirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tekshirmoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. yo'q qilmoq",
            "D. tashlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "false",
        answer: "D. noto'g'ri",
        options: [
            "A. to'g'ri",
            "B. haqiqat",
            "C. chin",
            "D. noto'g'ri"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "gift",
        answer: "B. sovg'a",
        options: [
            "A. xarid",
            "B. sovg'a",
            "C. to'lov",
            "D. sotuv"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "hunger",
        answer: "C. ochlik",
        options: [
            "A. chanqoqlik",
            "B. charchoq",
            "C. ochlik",
            "D. xursandlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "imagine",
        answer: "A. tasavvur qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tasavvur qilmoq",
            "B. unutmoq",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "D. mensimaslik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "journey",
        answer: "B. sayohat",
        options: [
            "A. ish",
            "B. sayohat",
            "C. o'yin",
            "D. tanaffus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "puzzle",
        answer: "D. jumboq",
        options: [
            "A. yechim",
            "B. topshiriq",
            "C. hikoya",
            "D. jumboq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "quite",
        answer: "A. ancha",
        options: [
            "A. ancha",
            "B. ozroq",
            "C. kamdan-kam",
            "D. hech qachon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "rather",
        answer: "B. ko'proq",
        options: [
            "A. kamroq",
            "B. ko'proq",
            "C. ba'zida",
            "D. har doim"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "specific",
        answer: "C. aniq",
        options: [
            "A. umumiy",
            "B. oddiy",
            "C. aniq",
            "D. tasodifiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "tour",
        answer: "A. sayohat",
        options: [
            "A. sayohat",
            "B. tushlik",
            "C. ish",
            "D. tanaffus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "trip",
        answer: "B. safar",
        options: [
            "A. ish",
            "B. safar",
            "C. tanaffus",
            "D. mashg'ulot"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "value",
        answer: "D. qiymat",
        options: [
            "A. xarajatlar",
            "B. qarzlar",
            "C. zarar",
            "D. qiymat"
        ]
    }
];
